sbi2-4u.com 2015-12-12

# Privacy Policy - The SiteSell Blog

We do not share your private personal information (ex., name, email address, street address, and phone number) with any other organizations or individuals. We keep all such information you provide to us, no matter how or why you provide it (ex., becoming an affiliate, ordering our products, etc.) completely confidential, and use it only for the purpose that you intended.

Only those employees with relevant business duties (ex., support staff) may access your private personal information, and only to perform their duties. They are subject to dismissal for any privacy violation.

We never provide any such information about our subscribers, customers or affiliates to any third party, except in the unusual event should we be required to do so by law.

As you browse SiteSell.com, Google Analytics and advertising cookies will be placed on your computer to collect demographic and interest information, but we do not tie the cookie to any personal information that you provide to us.

Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with SiteSell.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit [this page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

In addition, if you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you may use their [opt-out tool](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

In other words… your visit to blog.sitesell.com is entirely private and anonymous.
